[{"answer": "Oh. Oh, yeah.  No. This is a different one", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Called?  When", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "From the club.  You didn't answer", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You were asleep when I got home, yes", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " No, no I don't.  Are you sure", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " What do you mean?  You're where right now", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes, I believe so", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He is?  I didn't think you knew my friend. How do you know he's dead", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why? what is it?  Why did you make me wait out here", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Was there", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't know.  The guards say they've never seen him before", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "He's in the infirmary, being examined", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Where is he now", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Did you ask him who he is", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I missed you", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Me, too", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yeah... Call me at home.  I'll give you the number", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Where'd you come from", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I was", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What is this? Why didn't you tell me? What?... I don't remember any of this", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "He'll kill us", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm not positive... but... he knows", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm not positive... but... he knows", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You like it", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What deal", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Hey, my friend... How ya doin'", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You know who it is", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't think so.  Where was it that you think we've met", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No. No, I don't", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " You all right", "docId": "Lost-Highway.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You killed him", "qsentId": 34}]